<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BAVAGA</title><link>https://www.bavaga.com/</link><description>Recent content on BAVAGA</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Wilhelm Haas</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 22:51:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bavaga.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I Did It: My 'About Me' Page is Finally Live!</title><link>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/27/i-did-it-my-about-me-page-is-finally-live/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 22:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/27/i-did-it-my-about-me-page-is-finally-live/ posts</guid><description>It’s official! After much thought and a bit of procrastination, I’ve finally completed my About Me page.
It’s a space where you can get to know me better: who I am, what I’m passionate about, and why I created this blog. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re here for the first time or you&amp;rsquo;ve been following along for a while, I hope you enjoy this little window into my world.</description></item><item><title>Free Impressum &amp; Privacy Policy Generator for German Sites</title><link>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/18/legal-notice-generator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:02:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/18/legal-notice-generator/ posts</guid><description>Discover how I found an easy, free solution to create an Impressum and Privacy Policy for my German website without the need to provide personal information. I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the tools that saved me time and stress, and explain why they’re a great option for website owners targeting a German audience.</description></item><item><title>Build a Customizable Progress Indicator with Pure CSS: Harvey Ball Example</title><link>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/06/customizable-progress-indicator-pure-css-harvey-ball/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 01:25:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2023/01/06/customizable-progress-indicator-pure-css-harvey-ball/ posts</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to build a fully customizable progress indicator using pure CSS, featuring Harvey Ball-style visuals. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to easily adjust the size, color, and progress values with CSS variables. We&amp;rsquo;ll also cover how to keep values in check with clamping and explore some upcoming CSS features. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re working on a dashboard or just want to add a sleek visual element, this tutorial has you covered - no extra libraries needed!</description></item><item><title>Hello World - The Beginning of My Journey</title><link>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2022/12/31/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:36:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bavaga.com/blog/2022/12/31/hello-world/ posts</guid><description>Here I am, closing out 2022 by reaching an important personal goal:
I’ve launched my own blog. I’ve published my first post. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the first step in my mission. But no, my mission is far from accomplished: it’s only just getting started.
Personal Growth For a long time, I thought about taking this step but never had the courage to actually start my own blog.
Now, I’ve finally made it happen.</description></item></channel></rss>